<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>product on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>/tags/product/</link>
    <description>Recent content in product on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/product/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathing Chair</title>
      <link>/project/2018_breathing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_breathing/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview I&amp;rsquo;m submitting this project to ACM SIGGRAPH 2019 Posters.
  We present a Breathing Chair that changes its state and shape to prevent current sedentary lifestyle and help in shaping a healthy living habit. The Breathing chair tracks how long people have been sitting, and its surface swells physically like a mammal’s lung when people sit in the Breathing Chair for a long time. In so doing, it nudges people to stand up gently to avoid health risks of prolonged sitting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collective Juice</title>
      <link>/tmp/2018_collective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tmp/2018_collective/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview   Collective Juice is a physical product that collects different user&amp;rsquo;s emotions and tone together to reveal and visualizes the “mood” of the group/community.
Objective How might we collect responses to questions that can only be answered by humans? As the development of technology, we can find many answers online within just a second. Have we ever wondered how the other people think about the same question?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUMAN EXPERIENCE FOR TRANSHUMAN</title>
      <link>/project/2018_speculative/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_speculative/</guid>
      <description>XHuman: Educational Headset for transhumans to Experience “Human” in 2075 XHuman is an educational headset for transhumans who inplants superintelligence into their left brain which works for language, memory, calculation. This gadget stimulates your brain electrically and temporarily stops the neurotransmission between the brain chip and the brain. This feature enables transhumans to think as “Humans.&amp;rdquo;
        
How can Humans and Transhumans coexist towards a sustainable society in 2075?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LimpiDual Touch</title>
      <link>/project/2009_llimpidual/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2009_llimpidual/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview    LimpiDual Touch is the emerging interactive transparent display. Users can operate from the rear side of the screen while seeing both displayed images and their fingers. This feature resolves a finger occlusion problem. Additionally, it also works for multiple users. Two users can share an identical display from both sides and control displayed objects at one time. This feature will apply to a collaborative work and an entertainment application.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>