<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Service on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>http://iwabm.github.io/tags/service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Service on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://iwabm.github.io/tags/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES Service Design | 2017, Professiona Work
  DESIGN QUESTION: How should the role of an energy company change with focusing on a customer experience? In 2016, the deregulation of the electric power industry in Japan started on a full scale and a lot of emerging companies have been entering into the electtricity market. Chubu Electric Power Company (C-EPCO) must shift to a new paradigm of customer service to improve their retention capability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUTURE SUPERMARKET DESIGN INAGEYA</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2016_inageya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2016_inageya/</guid>
      <description>FUTURE SUPERMARKET DESIGN INAGEYA Business Design | 2016, Professional Work
  Design Question: What is &amp;ldquo;beyond&amp;rdquo; supermarket? In a situation that society and family structures are changing, a role of supermarket also needs to change in Japan. Clients were struggling for planning a strong concept of a next-generation supermarket in 2020 with consideration for a sustainable ecosystem and of course customer-first. Design Thinking: Dive into &amp;ldquo;the customer&amp;rdquo; Using IBM Design Thinking, we supported to ideate a brand-new future user experience and defined the concept of next-gen supermarket only in 2 days intensive design camp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daifuku Experience</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2015_daifuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2015_daifuku/</guid>
      <description>DAIFUKU EXPERIENCE UX/UI Design | 2015, Professiona Work
  Design Question: How do we build awareness for a global unified brand? Clients thought their website was becoming obsolete and wanted to enhance their brand using current web technologies and user-centered disciplines. And Daifuku has 20 branches in the world, so they wanted to provide global integrated contents and operations.
Our Approach: Service Ecosystem Design Based on a service design approach, we designed and proposed from a business organization to UX / UI and an infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Corporate Service Corps</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2014_csc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2014_csc/</guid>
      <description>IBM Corporate Service Corps Business Strategy Design | 2014, Professional Work
  Design Question: How do we establish a preferable future vision on a social level? IBM CSC(Corporate Service Corp) is one-month pro bono consulting program for developing countries addressing Energy, Economic Development, Transportation, Education, and Healthcare. I participated in the IBM pro bono Corporate Service Corps, addressing social issues in developing countries. I was one of a cross-border global IBM team in Mexico that sought to tackle the problems of gender violence by collaborating with the Mexico State Public Administration.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>