<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Service on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>http://iwabm.github.io/tags/service/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Service on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://iwabm.github.io/tags/service/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES Service Design | 2017, Professiona Work
  Objective Which direction should the electric power company aim for? In 2016, full-scale deregulation of the electricity industry in Japan has begun, and a lot of new and emerging companies have entered the electricity market. Chubu Electric Power Company (C-EPCO), a Japanese electricity utility provider for the mid-Chubu region of Honshu island, Japan, must shift to a new paradigm of customer service in order to improve its retention capability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUTURE SUPERMARKET DESIGN INAGEYA</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2016_inageya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2016_inageya/</guid>
      <description>FUTURE SUPERMARKET DESIGN INAGEYA Business Design | 2016, Professional Work
  Objective What should Inageya do to go &amp;ldquo;beyond&amp;rdquo; supermarket? Inagea is a long-established supermarket in Japan. However, in a situation that society and family structures are changing, a role of supermarket also needs to change in Japan. Clients were struggling for planning a strong concept of a next-generation supermarket in 2020 with consideration for a sustainable ecosystem from producers to consumers and of course customer-first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daifuku Experience</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2015_daifuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2015_daifuku/</guid>
      <description>DAIFUKU EXPERIENCE UX/UI Design | 2015, Professiona Work  Objective How does DAIFUKU build a globally unified brand? Clients thought their website was becoming obsolete and wanted to enhance their brand using current web technologies and user-centered disciplines. And Daifuku has 20 branches in the world, so they wanted to provide global integrated contents and operations.
Concept Redesign DAIFUKU corporate website and operations From the perspective of Business, Design and Technology, we designed and proposed from a business organization to UX / UI and an infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Corporate Service Corps</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2014_csc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2014_csc/</guid>
      <description>IBM Corporate Service Corps Civic Service Design | 2014, Professional Work  Objective How do we build a preferable future vision on a social level? IBM CSC(Corporate Service Corp) is one-month pro bono consulting program for developing countries addressing Energy, Economic Development, Transportation, Education, and Healthcare. I participated in the IBM pro bono Corporate Service Corps, addressing social issues in developing countries. I was one of a cross-border global IBM team in Mexico that sought to tackle the problems of gender violence by collaborating with IAPEM (the Mexico State Public Administration).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>