<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Masaki Iwabuchi on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Masaki Iwabuchi on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 00:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathing Chair</title>
      <link>/ms1/final/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Dec 2018 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ms1/final/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;Breathing Chair is a chair which changes its shape to make people stand up. When people sit for a long time, the chair breathes organically and deform into a difficult shape to sit. After a while, the chair quietly returns to its original state. It leads people toward a state of standing up naturally to prevent sedentary lifestyle.

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/305882686&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;problem&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our body is designed for regular movement, but most people spend the bulk of their day sitting still instead. Especially, knowledge workers sit at their desks during the day, commute by car, and relax on the couch watching TV or on their computers in the evenings.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An independent survey that Ergotron commissioned [1] found that nearly 70 percent of full-time American workers hate sitting, yet 86 percent are required to do it all day, every day. As a result, they are sitting on the chair for an average of 13 hours on weekdays. According to a study of weekday total sitting hours in 20 countries around the world, the median daily total sitting time for 20 countries was 300 minutes. Also, Japan and Saudi Arabia were the longest in 420 minutes and 20 countries [2].&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/18.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research results that the health risk is increased by sitting too much has been reported worldwide, and attention is rising. As a representative study on the risk of death, there are investigations in Australia [3] that tracked approximately 220,000 people over the age of 45 years for three years, compared to those with a sitting time of fewer than 4 hours per day over 8 hours 1.15 times, people with more than 11 hours have a 1.4 times higher risk of total mortality. According to the latest study, it has been pointed out that the sedentary life is also related to the function of the brain [4], and it is required that practical interventions aimed at reducing and replacing sedentary behavior with intermittent light intensity physical activity to help slow cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;related-work&#34;&gt;Related Work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two major approaches to tackle this problem. One is an approach from ergonomics. Furniture makers have been developing an ergonomic chair not to get tired even if it sits for a long time [5]. However, the latest studies show that it is more important to reduce the time to sit and increase the time to move. Deborah Rohm Young’s group [6] suggests that prolonged sitting is harmful to health because sedentary behaviors usually have an little energy expenditure of 1.5 metabolic equivalents (METs) or less while slow, leisurely walking or light housework uses around 2.5 METs, and vigorous to moderate physical activity uses around 3 METs or more.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/2.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other approach is from user experience design to increase the standing time of people. Height adjustable table [7] enables workers to work while standing. Buckley’s group reports that standing-based office work encourages signs of attenuating post-prandial glycaemic excursion [8]. However, Baker’s research group assessed that prolonged standing might also have health and productivity impacts [9]. Data that it is not good for your health whether you are sitting too hard or too standing has been reported.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/3.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple watch [10] provides another solution. It detects periods of no move of the person wearing it and urges him/her to stand up and walk. It can announce to the user at an appropriate timing for walking based on the biometric data, but the user may not perform the actual operation or accept the advice in some cases.
In summary, based on the human-centered design, these products consider how to provide comfort and a healthy posture on the premise of human physical characteristics and limitations.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;concept&#34;&gt;Concept&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breathing Chair offers the novel way to prevent prolonged sitting by chair breathing. When people sit for a long time, the chair breathes organically and deform into a difficult shape to sit. It leads people toward a state of standing up in a natural way. After a while, the chair quietly returns to its original state.
Our approach is from ontological design, in which objects shape human beings, unlike conventional human-centered product designs mentioned in previous studies. Escobar argues “We design tools, and these tools design us back” in his book of ontological design [11]. We synthesized with and created Breathing Chair based on this nondualism concept that our individuals, materials and the world are all united and that there is no center.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;discussion-of-shape&#34;&gt;Discussion of Shape&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the breathing chair, we explored some shapes of the optimal deforming chair.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/19.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A heating chair that makes users stand up as the temperature gets hot.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/9.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A folding chair that makes users stands up by changing the shape to a vertical shape.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/8.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An animal chair that changes into the shape of an animal and gives a more organic impression.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/6.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the ideation, we organized these four ideas on two axes.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/10.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One axis we considered was mechanical vs. organic. Mechanical way is functional for users. However, this chair makes people sudden change, and it is not our intention to let the user feel &amp;ldquo;being forced to a machine.&amp;rdquo; Sudden mechanical change seems ruthless and irritates users. Therefore, we judged that the organic way is more appropriate in this project and wanted users to think “the chair is also a living thing and so it cannot be helped.”



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/11.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other axis is state-changing vs. shape-changing. Chairs in the upper row change state like a cold state and a hot state, a shrinking state and a swelling state, whereas chairs in the lower row are only deforming from a chair to a different shape. We judged that the state-changing way is more appropriate because this way gives users more impression of living things.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/12.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result of evaluating with the above two axes, we finally chose the idea of Breathing Chair.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/13.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/14.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;implementation&#34;&gt;Implementation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding implementation, it consists of two functions. One is measuring the time sitting. The force sensor on the seating surface  measures the time since a person sits on the chair. The other is controlling breathing. In this prototype, we use the balloon, and it stretched when people were seated for a certain period.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/16.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Patel et al.&amp;rsquo;s research [12], it is important to walk up and walk around many times a day. Also, if you stand for two minutes every hour, lipid, blood sugar, and blood pressure will improve. Therefore, we adjusted the balloon to swell for about 2 minutes when the user continues sitting for 1 hour.
The state of actual operation is shown in the following image. We confirmed that the bulging of the balloon pushes the user forward.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/17.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;conclusion-and-future-work&#34;&gt;Conclusion and Future Work&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we propose the Breathing Chair which changes its shape to make people stand up to prevent prolonged sitting. When people sit for 1 hour, the chair breathes organically and deform into a difficult shape to sit. After 2 minutes, the chair quietly returns to its original state. It leads people toward a state of standing up in a natural way. We introduced the concept, design and running prototype.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for a future iteration, there are two considerations to improve the quality of the product. One is the form itself. In this prototype, we were able to confirm that the breathing chair creates the force to make people stand up, so we would like to consider more organic shape such as a breathable fabric instead of a balloon. The other is the configuration of parameters. It is better to adjust the interval according to the usage environment, the age of the user, the use case, etc. Regarding a future application, we would like to install this product to schools and offices and to lead sedentary people to healthy lifestyles by an organic breathing chair.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/15.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;reference&#34;&gt;Reference&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ergotron, Inc. 2013. Ergotron JustStand Survey &amp;amp; Index Report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bauman AE, Ainsworth B.,Sallis j, et al. 2011. The descriptive epidemiology of sitting: A 20-country comparison using the International Physical Activity Questionnaire (IPAQ). Am J Prev Med 2011; 41: 228-235.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Van der Ploeg HP, Chey T,Korda RJ, et al. 2012. Sitting time and all‐cause mortality risk in 222,497 Austrarian adults. Arch Intern Med 2012;172:494‐500.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wheeler MJ, Dempsey PC, Grace MS, et al. 2017. Sedentary behavior as a risk factor for cognitive decline? A focus on the influence of glycemic control in brain health. Alzheimers Dement (N Y). 2017;3(3):291-300. Published 2017 May 2. doi:10.1016/j.trci.2017.04.001&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Herman Millar. 1994. Aeron Chair: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hermanmiller.com/products/seating/office-chairs/aeron-chairs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://www.hermanmiller.com/products/seating/office-chairs/aeron-chairs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Young DR, Hivert MF, Alhassan S, Camhi SM, Ferguson JF, Katzmarzyk PT, Lewis CE, Owen N, Perry CK, Siddique J, Yong CM. 2016. Sedentary Behavior and Cardiovascular Morbidity and Mortality: A Science Advisory From the American Heart Association. Endorsed by The Obesity Societ; Physical Activity Committee of the Council on Lifestyle and Cardiometabolic Health; Council on Clinical Cardiology; Council on Epidemiology and Prevention; Council on Functional Genomics and Translational Biology; and Stroke Council. Circulation. 2016 Sep 27;134(13):e262-79. doi: 10.1161/CIR.0000000000000440. Epub 2016 Aug 15. Review.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Okamura. 2016. SW: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.okamura.com/en_us/products/categories/height_adjustable_tables/height_adjustable/sw/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://www.okamura.com/en_us/products/categories/height_adjustable_tables/height_adjustable/sw/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buckley JP, Mellor DD, Morris M, et al. 2014. Standing-based office work shows encouraging signs of attenuating post-prandial glycaemic excursion Occup Environ Med 2014;71:109-111.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baker R, Coenen P, Howie E, Lee J, Williamson A, Straker L. 2018. A detailed description of the short-term musculoskeletal and cognitive effects of prolonged  standing for office computer work. Ergonomics. 2018 Jul;61(7):877-890. doi: 10.&lt;sup&gt;1080&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;00140139&lt;/sub&gt;.2017.1420825. Epub 2018 Feb 7. PubMed PMID: 29388500.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple. 2018. Apple Watch Series 4: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apple.com/watch/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://www.apple.com/watch/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arturo Escobar. 2018. An Outline of Ontological in Designs for the Pluriverse. Durham: Duke University Press, 2018.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alpa V Patel, Maret L Maliniak, Erika Rees-Punia, Charles E Matthews, Susan M Gapstur. 2018. Prolonged Leisure Time Spent Sitting in Relation to Cause-Specific Mortality in a Large US Cohort, American Journal of Epidemiology, Volume 187, Issue 10, 1 October 2018, Pages 2151–2158.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Berlin: Animal Imitation</title>
      <link>/parsons/vrtrip1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/parsons/vrtrip1/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/image.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
You wanna experience VR space with pets? A completely new VR experience was born. If you wear this new VR headset, you can walk a foreign city with your pet. The difference from the VR experience so far is that pets can also wear VR goggles and pets can also experience a totally different place taking a walk. In addition, you can exchange your vision and pet&amp;rsquo;s vision. You can take a walk as if you were a pet, and a pet as if you were an owner. Please try experiencing this completely new VR.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;human-s-view&#34;&gt;Human&amp;rsquo;s view&lt;/h2&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/301936497&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;dog-s-view&#34;&gt;Dog&amp;rsquo;s view&lt;/h2&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/301936713&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated Intent for Final</title>
      <link>/ms1/intent2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2018 00:00:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ms1/intent2/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;final-statement&#34;&gt;Final Statement&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;problem-why&#34;&gt;Problem (Why)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are things which we cannot do by myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;solution-what&#34;&gt;Solution (What)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Use recursive power to do it by myself

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/300566889&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;design-process&#34;&gt;Design Process&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;brainstorming&#34;&gt;Brainstorming&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide9.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide10.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide11.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;concept-1&#34;&gt;Concept 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide12.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide13.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide14.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/300565438&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;concept-2&#34;&gt;Concept 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide15.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide16.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide17.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/300567236&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;concept-3&#34;&gt;Concept 3&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide18.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide19.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide20.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/300565209&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;feedback-and-update&#34;&gt;Feedback and Update&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide3.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/300566889&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;



&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/300566306&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;





&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide7.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intent for Final</title>
      <link>/ms1/intent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ms1/intent/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h4 id=&#34;context-domain-1&#34;&gt;Context - Domain 1&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;network-science&#34;&gt;Network Science&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first domain I want to research is Network Science. When I reviewed my exploration so far, I found I am interested in creating a network in any kind of way. For example, in 2D and 4D, I tried to create a network and connect people based on background careers or question-answer conversation. Previously I said that my domain is social computing, however, social computing was still broad and it was more intriguing for me to see it from the perspective of the network.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually network science covers very broad area because in the current our world, we are surrounded by bunch of networks such as hypertext, social network and transportation network and so on. I&amp;rsquo;m interested in what is networked and not networked, and what will happen if stand-alone things such as subjective feelings and body signalsare networked.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;context-domain-2&#34;&gt;Context - Domain 2&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;affective-interaction&#34;&gt;Affective Interaction&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 3D - 5D, I tried to implement the interaction through affective questions that can only be answered by people. Affective computing is one of the representative area of this field and researching development of systems and devices that can recognize, interpret, process, and simulate human affects. However, I want to focus on not an emotion recognition technology itself but an application of human affects as a designer.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;creative-precedents&#34;&gt;Creative Precedents&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;penal-systems-network&#34;&gt;Penal Systems Network&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Penal Systems Network is a relational mapping of world’s penal systems that evoke controversy: A network map of world countries connected to juridical topics whether or not they are being exercised and how they are being exercised such as death penalty, life imprisonment, parole, indefinite sentence, and amnesty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Context: Make a network of domestic data



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/3.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;feel-o-meter&#34;&gt;Feel-o-meter&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fuehlometer (Feel-o-meter) is an interactive art installation that shows the mood of a city by displaying it in the form of a monumental Smiley. The system allows to read emotions out of random people’s faces. The faces are analyzed by sophisticated software (contributed by the Fraunhofer Institut). The obtained mood data are then stored on a server and processed by the smiley to visualize the emotions in real-time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Context: Assemble moods of the city

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/nBstJ6_HMac&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;lauren-a-human-smart-home-intelligence&#34;&gt;LAUREN. A human smart home intelligence.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project attempts to become a human version of Amazon Alexa, a smart home intelligence for people in their own homes. The artist Lauren remotely watches over the person &lt;sup&gt;24&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;7&lt;/sub&gt; and controls all aspects of their home. Lauren aims to be better than an AI because she can understand them as a person and anticipate their needs. The relationship that emerges falls in the ambiguous space between human-machine and human-human.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Context: Make a network and relationship between people who do not know each other



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/4.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;electric-stimulus-to-face&#34;&gt;electric stimulus to face&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Daito Manabe experimented how might we control our face electrically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Context: Make a network of body signals

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/CvmE4TZfeuo&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-stack&#34;&gt;The Stack&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In The Stack, Benjamin Bratton proposes that these different genres of computation—smart grids, cloud platforms, mobile apps, smart cities, the Internet of Things, automation—can be seen not as so many species evolving on their own, but as forming a coherent whole: an accidental megastructure called The Stack that is both a computational apparatus and a new governing architecture. We are inside The Stack and it is inside of us. In an account that is both theoretical and technical, drawing on political philosophy, architectural theory, and software studies, Bratton explores six layers of The Stack: Earth, Cloud, City, Address, Interface, User. Each is mapped on its own terms and understood as a component within the larger whole built from hard and soft systems intermingling—not only computational forms but also social, human, and physical forces. This model, informed by the logic of the multilayered structure of protocol “stacks,” in which network technologies operate within a modular and vertical order, offers a comprehensive image of our emerging infrastructure and a platform for its ongoing reinvention.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Context: Devide network into layers&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/6.jpeg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;beeme&#34;&gt;BeeMe&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Halloween scientists at MIT&amp;rsquo;s Media Lab are embarking on a massive social experiment. Called BeeMe, the project will let internet users control a real human actor, suggesting, and collectively voting on, this person&amp;rsquo;s every action. New Atlas reached out to Niccolo Pescetelli, one of the creators behind the experiment, to find out exactly what is about to happen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Context: Make a collective decision and control human



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/7.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;design-questions-and-concepts-so-far&#34;&gt;Design Questions and Concepts so far&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;creative-questions&#34;&gt;Creative Questions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this research, I came up with the following creative questions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What will happen if stand-alone things such as subjective feelings and body signalsare networked?

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What happens when objects are networked? Can you synthesize or disassemble it?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How might we assemble individual affects and utilize them for individuals again?

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How will rewards and erroneous information affect collective decisions?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How much will a person&amp;rsquo;s free will be affected by the collective will?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;concepts&#34;&gt;Concepts&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Decompose network elements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Networked body signal&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Use network as a medium of art&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Control virtual challacter by collective decision&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visualize traffic of each layer of Stack (City, Earth and so on)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;discuss-in-the-class&#34;&gt;Discuss in the class&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;discuss-with-jerry-and-karen&#34;&gt;Discuss with Jerry and Karen&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of Jerry&amp;rsquo;s domain collective creation was similar to my domain. He was interested in collecting body signals and turning into some information, and I also curious about collecting emotions of the human. We discussed how to deal with elements of the interaction. Our common factors of interaction are people and the environment, and we debated what input and output we should use. I referred to some precedents Jerry had, and I found some interactions treated everybody equal, and the other one visualized information according to a person&amp;rsquo;s body heights. So the insight of discussion with Jerry was we can give a different look and feel according to how to handle input and output.
However, Karen pointed out that we were going into discussions of implementation deeply, and we found we should discuss &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo; perspective. Human augmentation, one of Karen&amp;rsquo;s domain, is also related to my domain. Our common aim is to expand the human&amp;rsquo;s perception. In discussion with Karen, I found I need to think about substantial problems from the perspective of the user and write down the question as the form of &amp;ldquo;How might we - ?&amp;rdquo;
Finally, I came up with the question &amp;ldquo;How might we make a network of countries&amp;rsquo; happiness to compare with standards of happiness?&amp;rdquo; in the discussion. But I thought my question still needed strong &amp;ldquo;why&amp;rdquo;. So I need more resarch to create future vision of network and human augmentation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;more-precedents&#34;&gt;More Precedents&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;mutual-human-actuation&#34;&gt;Mutual Human Actuation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Human actuation is the idea of using people to provide large-scale force feedback to users. The key idea is to run pairs of users at the same time and have them provide human actuation to each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came up with one question from this work: How might we connect activities which are completely different but mutualy complementary?&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/JKGdQjx-_BI&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h2 id=&#34;sense-roid-emotional-haptic-communication-with-yourself&#34;&gt;Sense-Roid: Emotional Haptic Communication with Yourself&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What type of emotions could be obtained if you were able to hug yourself?

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//www.youtube.com/embed/vw5pFZaiuCg&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; allowfullscreen title=&#34;YouTube Video&#34;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;fight-with-myself&#34;&gt;Fight with myself&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a Japanese geek blog, a father made a system which decreases the time of changing his child&amp;rsquo;s cloth. The problem for this father was that his child often takes time to change his cloth in the busy morning. So he projected images of the child&amp;rsquo;s changing cloth in the past and let him compete with himself in the past. In this kind of way of gamification, his child thought he didn&amp;rsquo;t want to lose to himself and became to change his cloth as quickly as possible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came up with one question from this work: How might we make a network with ourselves in the past to improve ourselves?&amp;lt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/10.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;updated-questions-and-concepts&#34;&gt;Updated Questions and Concepts&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-might-we-connect-activities-which-are-completely-different-but-mutualy-complementary&#34;&gt;How might we connect activities which are completely different but mutualy complementary?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;For example, if there is a person somewhere who wants to push objects and there is a person who wants to draw some object at the same time, can we connect those activities that are totally individually occurring and make mutually complementary relationships?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-might-we-make-a-network-with-ourselves-in-the-past-to-improve-ourselves&#34;&gt;How might we make a network with ourselves in the past to improve ourselves?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In life, the most challenging enemy is myself. To keep improving, can we make a connection with ourselves in the past via some kind of inormation?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;direction-of-prototype&#34;&gt;Direction of Prototype&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;seek-activities-which-are-completely-different-but-mutualy-complementary&#34;&gt;Seek activities which are completely different but mutualy complementary&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;seek-a-valuable-information-to-track-for-keeping-improving-myself&#34;&gt;Seek a valuable information to track for keeping improving myself&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the time to turn off the light of the bedroom&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ChanoMa</title>
      <link>/project/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h5 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chubu Electric Power(C-EP) supplies electricity to 10 million households in Japan. ChanoMa (means &amp;ldquo;Living Room&amp;rdquo;) is a service for a dual-income households with a small children among their customers to tighten family bonds.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide14.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is part of the project’s final design that I delivered to the client. A special feature of using ChanoMa is that App plays and communicates with children when parents are busy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to our many interviews with working mothers, they are the busiest with cooking and houseworks for 30 minutes since they came home. ChanoMa plays with children using safe contents at that time, and helps parents.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, by recording children&amp;rsquo;s daily responses and sharing these with their parents, they can understand children&amp;rsquo;s hidden feelings and preferences. As a future expansion, it will work as a platform of the entire family members including grandparents as if they are in the same living room even if they live far apart.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal of this project was to tighten family bonds and make C-EP’s brand an essential part of family life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;my-role&#34;&gt;My Role&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was employed as a project manager and a lead UX designer of an 10-person team consisting of designers, engineers and business strategists and managed the project from the concept creation to the implementation phases using methodologies of Design Thinking, Lean Startup and Agile Development.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide24.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is actually an iterative journey of building, measuring and learning. With continuous discussion with users, clients, designers, engineers and business strategists, finally we developed and delivered an appropriate service for users.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide11.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am certified as both a practitioner of IBM Design Thinking and a Scrum Master, which means I can work consistently end to end, , as a professional user experience designer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Using design thinking, while focusing on customer-oriented thinking, we define the strong concept eventually to be released as a service running in the society. With the concept of lean startup, we verify and grow the service concept as a feasible business model. Finally we implement the business ecosystem designed with such a way of thinking to the world with agile development.

As a project manager and professional UX designer, I contributed to the project from the concept phase to the agile development phase. In terms of technology, customer experience and sustainable business model, my team designed entire new business ecosystem of the client.

In the concept phase, I planned a Design Thinking workshop with clients and created the initial concept of the service, prior to narrowing this down to a series of actionable steps in consideration of the concept’s implementation. Additionally, in the subsequent development phase, I have worked on continuously improving the quality of the product through a process of iterative prototyping and user evaluation. --&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
In 2016, new policy of deregulation of the electricity industry in Japan has begun, and a lot of new and emerging companies and startups have entered the electricity market and acquire users by user-centric services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;b&gt;C-EP must&lt;/b&gt; shift to a client first company and &lt;b&gt;provide user-centered services in order to improve its retention capability.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide7.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
At the beginning, in the concept phase, I facilitated 2-days IBM Design Thinking workshop with clients, created the initial concept for a new service. We divided the members into 2 teams (personas) and eventually created 6 promising concepts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;target-user-and-insight&#34;&gt;Target User and Insight&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide3.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
We decided &lt;b&gt;a dual-income working mother&lt;/b&gt; as a primary user. In Japan, 49% of households are dual-income families in urban area and It is expected that this figure will continue to rise in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
According to 10 interviews with working mother, we found &lt;b&gt;how hard working parents take care of little children.&lt;/b&gt; When a working mother comes back to the home, she must do many houseworks with taking care of children. And finally we found 2 core insights we should tackle with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
One is the problem that &lt;b&gt;recent mothers often handed out a smartphone to a child when they were busy and showed YouTube and animation.&lt;/b&gt; &lt;b&gt;It causes less communication between parents and children.&lt;/b&gt; Also, some young mothers even lose a way how to take care of children. They feel guilty to rely on a smartphone, but they can not quit it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
The other insight is &lt;b&gt;mothers don&amp;rsquo;t know children&amp;rsquo;s feelings and preferences well.&lt;/b&gt; According to our interview, even mothers who are communicating with children usually say that they do not understand children&amp;rsquo;s feelings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;initial-core-concept&#34;&gt;Initial Core Concept&lt;/h5&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide9.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With iterative prototyping in collaboration with C-EP members, I came up with the idea that IoT toy plays and communicates with children when parents are busy. By recording children’s daily responses and sharing these with their parents, family members can understand their hidden feelings and preferences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;experience-design&#34;&gt;Experience Design&lt;/h5&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide10.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide12.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide15.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
Considering the project period and budget constraints, I decided to launch the App version as the first MVP.
I regarded working mothers to &lt;b&gt;rely on smartphones as a new habit&lt;/b&gt; and turn it into positive activities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We developed an iOS app that can communicate with children when parents handed out a smartphone to them. By recording their daily responses and sharing these with parents, &lt;b&gt;the family members are able to understand the children’s hidden feelings and preferences.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;collaborative-studio&#34;&gt;Collaborative Studio&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide13.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide16.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide17.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
As a project manager, I planned to improve the parts of the product the needed it based on the research results. I opened a collaborative studio in which multiple members in teams could simultaneously discuss various topics from a business plan to elements of UI that needed to be improved and tried to create an appropriate experience. I repeated this whole-day workshop with not only internal designers but also C-EP members for 3 rounds and then had a vote to decide the design direction with everyone’s opinion included.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;ui-design&#34;&gt;UI Design&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide18.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide19.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide20.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide21.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide22.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide23.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
For this project, it was necessary to create designs for iOS platforms because it was the most major platform among C-EP customers. We performed 30 interviews and improved our product iteratively. Using InVision, we performed interviews with a moving prototype mockup. Finally, we fixed requirements of comprehensive services and proceeded to the following development phase.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/122.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;finalize-ux-ui-in-sprints-of-development&#34;&gt;Finalize UX/UI in sprints of development&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the subsequent development phase, I have been working on continuously improving the quality of the product through a process of iterative prototyping and user evaluation. I have the certification of both a practitioner of IBM Design Thinking and a Scrum Master, so I can work consistently end to end from the concept creation to implementation phases as a professional user experience designer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally my team designed and finalized 94 screens and interactions in the development phase.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/123.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;result&#34;&gt;Result&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the implementation. we performed a qualitative and quantitative user evaluation. 234 dual-income households with children tested this App for 2 weeks, and 75% of people evaluated &amp;ldquo;Good (55%)&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Very Good (20%)&amp;rdquo; against the whole concept. Therefore, the client decide to launch this App in the next year cycle with considering qualitative feedback comments. Currently, the client continues to develop Android version and they are planning to release this product in 2019.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The items of evaluation is the following (according to AARRR model):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quantitative survey

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you sympathize with the concept?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Do you want to download and use this application?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Qualitative comments

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What are the pros and cons of this application?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Is there any other feature you want?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analysis of data log

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Which function was most used?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Which function kept being used most?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;learning&#34;&gt;Learning&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
I think service Design is Co-creation. Product design is a process of exploring an appropriate ecosystem comprising everyone, that is created by everyone, and is provided for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide8.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide25.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide26.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;project-schedule&#34;&gt;Project Schedule&lt;/h5&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/100.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Period: 02/2017 - 01/2018&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Method: User-Centered Design, Agile engineering, Lean Startup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MTA Smart Metrocard</title>
      <link>/project/2018_mta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_mta/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h5 id=&#34;project-overview&#34;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I personally tried to redesign MTA services because NYC subway riding experience is uncomfortable for me; dirty platform, unexpected stop, morning/evening rush and so on. I conducted the entire design process to specify inconvenient element of the subway and improve services of MTA.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;my-role&#34;&gt;My Role&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I conducted the whole design process from interviewing with users, defining problem, ideation, prototyping and evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current research (&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nycedc.com/blog-entry/transportation-trends-nyc&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;source&lt;/a&gt;) shows that &lt;b&gt;subway and bus ridership has declined&lt;/b&gt; while ridership through ride-sharing services like Lyft and Uber has increased. App-based services are based on a great UX and are increasing their users dramatically.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Therefore, to increase a retention rate, MTA needs to provide the user-centered service for the purpose of getting access easily to the metro, on time, without having a bad experience.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/research1.png&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  &lt;h4&gt;Data: Transportation Trends in NYC&lt;/h4&gt;
  
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From interviewing with real users, it turned out that &lt;b&gt;NYC commuters sometimes have a frustration that they want to catch a train but cannot because they don&amp;rsquo;t have enough money in the metro card.&lt;/b&gt; In this moment, they have to go back to a ticket vending machine and wait in a long line to refill your card. This is really frustrating and painful experience.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/vend.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To solve this problem, I developed the idea of smart metrocard which enables users to refill the money anytime and anywhere. Subway users can refill money through the App and enter the platform without using a ticket vending machine.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/card.png&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  &lt;h4&gt;Smart Metrocard&lt;/h4&gt;
  
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This proposal is a little bit radical because the physical metrocard also need to be intelligent in order to reflect real-time refilling money from the App. However, this smart metrocard infrastructure is adopted by many countries such as Germany, France and Japan, and they don’t have a frustration of purchasing train tickets.
&lt;iframe width=&#34;442&#34; height=&#34;935&#34; src=&#34;//invis.io/TCO7886KGHS&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;result&#34;&gt;Result&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this design challenge, I conducted the user interview using the invision mockup, basic function is accepted by the user and we can plan a next iteration.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/eva.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;design-process&#34;&gt;Design Process&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;New York city commuters are primary user group and travelers are second user group because they are the biggest user groups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From my research, there are 1.5 million daily-use commuters in NYC and over 60 million temporary-use traveller in a year. Also, they’re creating over $500M per month in total. They account for the majority of MTA&amp;rsquo;s revenue.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interviewing with a real user and confirming our assumption at the beginning is the fastest way to define problems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I conducted interviews with 3 friends of mine. 2 of them are commuters and other 1 is traveller. I confirmed their process to use the subway and extracted their pain points from this interview.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found commuters have frustration especially in rush hour. They hate time consuming to make a line to refill a metrocard and crowded train. Also, travellers have a trouble to sightseeing. They feel the entrance is narrow for big suitcase, time is not accurate and platform is dirty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, I converged the pain points and categorized 3 main frustration area from the interview. This is the problem related to ticket machines, platform and train schedule. These areas needs to be solved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide7.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide12.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Based on the specified pain points and directions, I conducted the brainstorming and created bold ideas. I came up with 10 following ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Touch &amp;amp; Go by smartphone&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gateless entry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fingerprint entry&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Refill using App&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Free wifi spot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Library in the platform&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bigger entrance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visualize maintenance status&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visualize realtime train operation status&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;visualize real train location on the map&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide13.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;!-- 


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide8.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide9.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide10.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide11.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt; --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the prioritization is the most important part because we must decide the solution and discard other solutions in this timing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this time, I used the prioritization grid which I used in my IBM career. This grid has 2 axis. One is desirability for the user and the other is feasibility in terms of technology and business. Using this 2 axis, we can evaluate the idea from design, business and technology.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/pri2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I arranged the idea using this chart and decided to pick up the idea that is in the No-Brainer area.
I finally chose the &amp;ldquo;Refill using App&amp;rdquo; idea because there is other competitors in the other idea in the No-Brainer area.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide14.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After defining the solution, I moved to the implementation phase. I drew the storyboard, content map and wireframes. My policy is drawing an experience in the storyboard. It should not be functional because it verifies the experience we&amp;rsquo;re thinking. For me, the prototype is a work to improve the resolution from 1 shot idea, 6 shots storyboards, to an interactive mockup.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide16.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide18.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide19.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;solution&#34;&gt;Solution&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;smart-metrocard-app&#34;&gt;Smart Metrocard App&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/sol.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
After prototyping, I conducted the user interview using the invision mockup because of the limited timeline. However, project success is measured by both quantitative and qualitative to judge properly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of quantitative perspective, we can test the time to refill money via App compared with making a line in front of a vending machine. We need to evaluate practical effects of the project using quantitative data. Also, in terms of qualitative measure, user interview should be conducted in the evaluation stage. I can confirm more emotional effects for the user.
&lt;!--
In this design challenge, I conducted the user interview using the invision mockup, however, some functions didn’t  work well such as the timing of registering credit card information. I think the concept that decreasing user’s frustration of refilling card was accepted by the user because in the user interview users mentioned they need these App. However, detailed functions still have a possibility to improve. --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/eva.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;learning&#34;&gt;Learning&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;!-- ## What is the tradeoffs?
In this design challenge, I set the project period is 5 days, 40h. So tradeoff between time and work was challenging. I know I need time to prototype and evaluate, however it is also important to define a right problem. So I limited the number of interviewees and implemented the minimum story. In doing so, I focus on doing the whole process with considering time limitation.

## What did I learn? --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I work in a project, I think the following two part is the most important.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One is defining the right problem because it is meaningless to solve the wrong problem. In this project, I conducted several user interviews to explore the problem and verify our assumption. Going out of the office and listening to the voice of real users is the start point of the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other is making as soon as possible trying multiple iterations. We cannot deliver a perfect product in the first iteration. We need to continue quick prototype and validate the experience in each time. In this project, I couldn’t take enough time to continue iterative cycles because of the limited timeline, but I need to manage at least 2 prototyping cycles to improve the final quality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;design-timeline&#34;&gt;Design Timeline&lt;/h5&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project Type

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Private | UX Design Challenge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase / Period

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Empathize, Define, Ideate, Prototype, Test&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 / 2018 (40h)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sole Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Method / Technology

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User-Centered Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Target Device: iOS App&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>/project/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h5 id=&#34;project-overview&#34;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had the opportunity to join the Research Methods in Interaction Design course at the School of Visual Arts. Our instructor Jodi Leo, Executive Director of User Experience at Critical Mass, led us to collaborate with the Research team at Uber to optimize efficiency for Uber drivers during the pick up at the JFK airport.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;my-role&#34;&gt;My Role&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I conducted interviews with Uber drivers, conducted secondary research, developed personas, project management, synthesis, concept/use case design, and designed the presentation narrative.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/lent1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;problem&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We called with Sam Eldersveld, Director of Operations Research at Uber, and we learned that Uber thought the &lt;b&gt;perfect pickup&lt;/b&gt; is the most important factor of the User Experience. The moment of pickup is when the driver and the rider meet for the first time. Both drivers and riders are nervous and frustrating in this moment because drivers want to finish the work without trouble and riders want to get to the destination quickly. If the entrance of this interaction is uncomfortable, the subsequent ride experience will also be unpleasant.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/int.png&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  &lt;h4&gt;Interview Material&lt;/h4&gt;
  
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;field-research&#34;&gt;Field Research&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We conducted our field research at JFK airport. It is one of the places where perfect pickup is difficult because of crowed cars and peoples, complicated terminal numbers and exits.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/air.png&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  &lt;h4&gt;Field Research and Interview with the Driver&lt;/h4&gt;
  
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We interviewed with a real driver how to do his work usually. We negotiated an untraditional ride: circling around the JFK airport for a 20 minute interview session.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the interview, we confirmed that he had a problem to pick up a rider in the airport. Our driver told that he had a mistake that he picked up the wrong person who has a same first name because this passenger was so in a hurry. Also, he had a language problem because sometimes people who cannot speak English ride especially in the airport. We understood how difficult to pick up a right person perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, we used AEIOU (Activities, Environments, Interactions, Objects, Users) templates as a framework to gather notable findings and we recorded all interactions and experiences we had.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/lent2.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to the field research, the problem is that &lt;b&gt;Uber drivers have a language problem&lt;/b&gt; in the airport ride because sometimes passengers cannot speak English. &lt;b&gt;This causes unjustifiable low ratings of drivers&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;define-problem&#34;&gt;Define Problem&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the interview, we debriefed our findings and designed a persona based on our talk with the driver. Just to note, there are other personas within the Uber driver community (young, single, female, temporary, etc). In the context of perfecting the pickup at JFK airport, solutions should be applied to all Uber drivers.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/15.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/125.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/128.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From gained insights of field research, we developed a user flow and mockup screens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;explore-solution&#34;&gt;Explore Solution&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We met after classes to conduct brainstorming and create solution. A few themes we began to build upon:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The driver has a language problem when the passenger cannot speak English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The driver sometimes cannot recognize the accurate pickup location&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/brain.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the ideation, we began to segment the Uber driver journey to visualize the complete end to end experience and look for opportunities to optimize the pickup process. We also designed a journey map for the passenger side as well.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/17.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/1.png&#34; /&gt;



&lt;figcaption data-pre=&#34;Figure &#34; data-post=&#34;:&#34; &gt;
  &lt;h4&gt;To-Be User Journey Map&lt;/h4&gt;
  
&lt;/figcaption&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;prototype-perfecting-the-pickup-regardless-of-language&#34;&gt;Prototype: Perfecting the Pickup regardless of language&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/131.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/132.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/133.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/134.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;result&#34;&gt;Result&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our team pitched our research and mockups to the class and really valuable feedback around the viability of our solutions. The feedback to focus on the functionality and flow of the driver interface is reflected in the iterations that have been made on this document.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/2.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/23.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;learning&#34;&gt;Learning&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think user interview needs not just a talking skill but a well-prepared strategy. To have a good preparation enables us to extract a good insight from user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this class, the professor told us these strategies of interview. For example, we should go to interview with at least 3 people and devided the role separately. One focus on the interview, another one focus on the minutes, and the final one focus on recording. It means interviewing is not only just a talking, but also a strategic activity. Another strategy is to prepare questions beforehand. To think about why we ask this question and what we want to extract is the most important part of the interview. Without these thinkings, our interview will be lost the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;design-timeline&#34;&gt;Design Timeline&lt;/h5&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Project Type

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Academic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Company: Uber&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Instructor: Jodi Leo, VP of Product Design at CapTap&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Class: Research Methods&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team with

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sandra Gatica Morales, Colleen Brogan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Method / Technology

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User-Centered Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Target Device: Mobile&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tasks

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interviews, User research, UX Design, Acquisition design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Output

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sketches ( design iterations and user flows)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interview Footage, Synthesis, and Findings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;User Acquisition research&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Design and functionality recommendations proposal deck&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Final assets (presentation poster board)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biography</title>
      <link>/ms1/career/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ms1/career/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Masaki is an interaction and service designer based in NY.
His work examines the reciprocal relationships between science, technology and their influence on human identity, subjectivity, and collective culture.
He holds the MFA degree in Design and Technology at Parsons School of Design. Previously he worked at IBM for 10 years as a UX designer.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Design Manifesto: Goodbye Human, Hello Alien.</title>
      <link>/publication/manifesto/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publication/manifesto/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MJ Button</title>
      <link>/ms1/highline/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ms1/highline/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;observation-research-ideation&#34;&gt;Observation, Research, Ideation&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide3.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide7.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide8.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide9.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide10.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide11.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide12.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide13.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide14.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide15.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide16.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide17.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide18.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide19.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;prototype&#34;&gt;Prototype&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img2/Slide1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img2/Slide2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img2/Slide3.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img2/Slide4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img2/Slide5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img2/Slide6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;test-iteration-1&#34;&gt;Test: Iteration 1&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/295098769&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide8.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;test-iteration-2&#34;&gt;Test: Iteration 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide9.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/295101278&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide11.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;test-iteration-3&#34;&gt;Test: Iteration 3&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide12.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/295102379&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide14.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;test-iteration-4&#34;&gt;Test: Iteration 4&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide15.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/295103357&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide17.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;future-iteration&#34;&gt;Future Iteration&lt;/h2&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img3/Slide18.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5D: Collective Transition</title>
      <link>/ms1/5d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 01:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ms1/5d/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide3.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide7.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide8.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide9.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide10.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4D: Collective Aroma</title>
      <link>/ms1/4d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ms1/4d/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide3.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide7.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide8.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D: Collective Juice</title>
      <link>/ms1/3d/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/ms1/3d/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide3.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide7.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/Slide8.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathing Chair</title>
      <link>/project/2018_breathing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_breathing/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h5 id=&#34;project-overview&#34;&gt;Project Overview&lt;/h5&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/305882686&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;We present a Breathing Chair that changes its state and shape to prevent current sedentary lifestyle and help in shaping a healthy living habit. The Breathing chair tracks how long people have been sitting, and its surface swells physically like a mammal’s lung when people sit in the Breathing Chair for a long time. In so doing, it nudges people to stand up gently to avoid health risks of prolonged sitting. After a while, the Breathing chair quietly shrinks to its original state organically. This state-changing aspect of the Breathing Chair is almost physical reminder for people to stand up and leads them to shape a healthy lifestyle. In this paper, we describe the concept, design, and implementation method of the Breathing Chair. We also conducted the preliminary qualitative study amongst a sample of seven users and demonstrated the nudging aspect of Breathing Chair. Finally, we presented how it can be used for future applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;problem&#34;&gt;Problem&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our body is designed for regular movement, but most people spend the bulk of their day sitting still instead. Especially, knowledge workers sit at their desks during the day, commute by car, and relax on the couch watching TV or on their computers in the evenings.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An independent survey that Ergotron commissioned [1] found that nearly 70 percent of full-time American workers hate sitting, yet 86 percent are required to do it all day, every day. As a result, they are sitting on the chair for an average of 13 hours on weekdays. According to a study of weekday total sitting hours in 20 countries around the world, the median daily total sitting time for 20 countries was 300 minutes. Also, Japan and Saudi Arabia were the longest in 420 minutes and 20 countries [2].&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/18.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Research results that the health risk is increased by sitting too much has been reported worldwide, and attention is rising. As a representative study on the risk of death, there are investigations in Australia [3] that tracked approximately 220,000 people over the age of 45 years for three years, compared to those with a sitting time of fewer than 4 hours per day over 8 hours 1.15 times, people with more than 11 hours have a 1.4 times higher risk of total mortality. According to the latest study, it has been pointed out that the sedentary life is also related to the function of the brain [4], and it is required that practical interventions aimed at reducing and replacing sedentary behavior with intermittent light intensity physical activity to help slow cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;related-work&#34;&gt;Related Work&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two major approaches to tackle this problem. One is an approach from ergonomics. Furniture makers have been developing an ergonomic chair not to get tired even if it sits for a long time [5]. However, the latest studies show that it is more important to reduce the time to sit and increase the time to move. Deborah Rohm Young’s group [6] suggests that prolonged sitting is harmful to health because sedentary behaviors usually have an little energy expenditure of 1.5 metabolic equivalents (METs) or less while slow, leisurely walking or light housework uses around 2.5 METs, and vigorous to moderate physical activity uses around 3 METs or more.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/2.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other approach is from user experience design to increase the standing time of people. Height adjustable table [7] enables workers to work while standing. Buckley’s group reports that standing-based office work encourages signs of attenuating post-prandial glycaemic excursion [8]. However, Baker’s research group assessed that prolonged standing might also have health and productivity impacts [9]. Data that it is not good for your health whether you are sitting too hard or too standing has been reported.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/3.jpg&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apple watch [10] provides another solution. It detects periods of no move of the person wearing it and urges him/her to stand up and walk. It can announce to the user at an appropriate timing for walking based on the biometric data, but the user may not perform the actual operation or accept the advice in some cases.
In summary, based on the human-centered design, these products consider how to provide comfort and a healthy posture on the premise of human physical characteristics and limitations.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;concept&#34;&gt;Concept&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Breathing Chair offers the novel way to prevent prolonged sitting by chair breathing. When people sit for a long time, the chair breathes organically and deform into a difficult shape to sit. It leads people toward a state of standing up in a natural way. After a while, the chair quietly returns to its original state.
Our approach is from ontological design, in which objects shape human beings, unlike conventional human-centered product designs mentioned in previous studies. Escobar argues “We design tools, and these tools design us back” in his book of ontological design [11]. We synthesized with and created Breathing Chair based on this nondualism concept that our individuals, materials and the world are all united and that there is no center.&lt;/p&gt;




&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;discussion-of-shape&#34;&gt;Discussion of Shape&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition to the breathing chair, we explored some shapes of the optimal deforming chair.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/19.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A heating chair that makes users stand up as the temperature gets hot.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/9.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A folding chair that makes users stands up by changing the shape to a vertical shape.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/8.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An animal chair that changes into the shape of an animal and gives a more organic impression.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/6.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the ideation, we organized these four ideas on two axes.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/10.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One axis we considered was mechanical vs. organic. Mechanical way is functional for users. However, this chair makes people sudden change, and it is not our intention to let the user feel &amp;ldquo;being forced to a machine.&amp;rdquo; Sudden mechanical change seems ruthless and irritates users. Therefore, we judged that the organic way is more appropriate in this project and wanted users to think “the chair is also a living thing and so it cannot be helped.”



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/11.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The other axis is state-changing vs. shape-changing. Chairs in the upper row change state like a cold state and a hot state, a shrinking state and a swelling state, whereas chairs in the lower row are only deforming from a chair to a different shape. We judged that the state-changing way is more appropriate because this way gives users more impression of living things.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/12.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a result of evaluating with the above two axes, we finally chose the idea of Breathing Chair.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/13.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/14.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;implementation&#34;&gt;Implementation&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regarding implementation, it consists of two functions. One is measuring the time sitting. The force sensor on the seating surface  measures the time since a person sits on the chair. The other is controlling breathing. In this prototype, we use the balloon, and it stretched when people were seated for a certain period.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/16.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;According to Patel et al.&amp;rsquo;s research [12], it is important to walk up and walk around many times a day. Also, if you stand for two minutes every hour, lipid, blood sugar, and blood pressure will improve. Therefore, we adjusted the balloon to swell for about 2 minutes when the user continues sitting for 1 hour.
The state of actual operation is shown in the following image. We confirmed that the bulging of the balloon pushes the user forward.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/17.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;conclusion-and-future-work&#34;&gt;Conclusion and Future Work&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this paper, we propose the Breathing Chair which changes its shape to make people stand up to prevent prolonged sitting. When people sit for 1 hour, the chair breathes organically and deform into a difficult shape to sit. After 2 minutes, the chair quietly returns to its original state. It leads people toward a state of standing up in a natural way. We introduced the concept, design and running prototype.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for a future iteration, there are two considerations to improve the quality of the product. One is the form itself. In this prototype, we were able to confirm that the breathing chair creates the force to make people stand up, so we would like to consider more organic shape such as a breathable fabric instead of a balloon. The other is the configuration of parameters. It is better to adjust the interval according to the usage environment, the age of the user, the use case, etc. Regarding a future application, we would like to install this product to schools and offices and to lead sedentary people to healthy lifestyles by an organic breathing chair.



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/15.gif&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&#34;reference&#34;&gt;Reference&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ergotron, Inc. 2013. Ergotron JustStand Survey &amp;amp; Index Report.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bauman AE, Ainsworth B.,Sallis j, et al. 2011. The descriptive epidemiology of sitting: A 20-country comparison using the International Physical Activity Questionnaire (IPAQ). Am J Prev Med 2011; 41: 228-235.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Van der Ploeg HP, Chey T,Korda RJ, et al. 2012. Sitting time and all‐cause mortality risk in 222,497 Austrarian adults. Arch Intern Med 2012;172:494‐500.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wheeler MJ, Dempsey PC, Grace MS, et al. 2017. Sedentary behavior as a risk factor for cognitive decline? A focus on the influence of glycemic control in brain health. Alzheimers Dement (N Y). 2017;3(3):291-300. Published 2017 May 2. doi:10.1016/j.trci.2017.04.001&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Herman Millar. 1994. Aeron Chair: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.hermanmiller.com/products/seating/office-chairs/aeron-chairs/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://www.hermanmiller.com/products/seating/office-chairs/aeron-chairs/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Young DR, Hivert MF, Alhassan S, Camhi SM, Ferguson JF, Katzmarzyk PT, Lewis CE, Owen N, Perry CK, Siddique J, Yong CM. 2016. Sedentary Behavior and Cardiovascular Morbidity and Mortality: A Science Advisory From the American Heart Association. Endorsed by The Obesity Societ; Physical Activity Committee of the Council on Lifestyle and Cardiometabolic Health; Council on Clinical Cardiology; Council on Epidemiology and Prevention; Council on Functional Genomics and Translational Biology; and Stroke Council. Circulation. 2016 Sep 27;134(13):e262-79. doi: 10.1161/CIR.0000000000000440. Epub 2016 Aug 15. Review.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Okamura. 2016. SW: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.okamura.com/en_us/products/categories/height_adjustable_tables/height_adjustable/sw/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://www.okamura.com/en_us/products/categories/height_adjustable_tables/height_adjustable/sw/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Buckley JP, Mellor DD, Morris M, et al. 2014. Standing-based office work shows encouraging signs of attenuating post-prandial glycaemic excursion Occup Environ Med 2014;71:109-111.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Baker R, Coenen P, Howie E, Lee J, Williamson A, Straker L. 2018. A detailed description of the short-term musculoskeletal and cognitive effects of prolonged  standing for office computer work. Ergonomics. 2018 Jul;61(7):877-890. doi: 10.&lt;sup&gt;1080&lt;/sup&gt;&amp;frasl;&lt;sub&gt;00140139&lt;/sub&gt;.2017.1420825. Epub 2018 Feb 7. PubMed PMID: 29388500.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Apple. 2018. Apple Watch Series 4: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.apple.com/watch/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://www.apple.com/watch/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Arturo Escobar. 2018. An Outline of Ontological in Designs for the Pluriverse. Durham: Duke University Press, 2018.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Alpa V Patel, Maret L Maliniak, Erika Rees-Punia, Charles E Matthews, Susan M Gapstur. 2018. Prolonged Leisure Time Spent Sitting in Relation to Cause-Specific Mortality in a Large US Cohort, American Journal of Epidemiology, Volume 187, Issue 10, 1 October 2018, Pages 2151–2158.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AR Businesscard</title>
      <link>/project/2018_ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_ar/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h5 id=&#34;demo-video&#34;&gt;Demo Video&lt;/h5&gt;


&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&#34;//player.vimeo.com/video/310200898&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
 &lt;/div&gt;


&lt;h5 id=&#34;project-information&#34;&gt;Project Information&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Phase / Period

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Concept, Design, Build&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;102/ 2018 (1 week)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Team / Role

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Sole Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maker, Coder&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Method / Technology

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iterative coding&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unity, Vuforia, C++&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;!-- 


&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/1.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/2.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/3.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/4.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/5.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt;



&lt;figure&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;img/6.png&#34; /&gt;


&lt;/figure&gt; --&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
