<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Speculative on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>http://iwabm.github.io/tags/speculative/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Speculative on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://iwabm.github.io/tags/speculative/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Human experience for Transhuman</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2018_singular/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2018_singular/</guid>
      <description>Human experience for Transhuman Speculative Design | 2018, Academic Work | ONGOING  *This project is still ongoing Settings What kind of tools are used by children who were born transhuman in the age of post-singularity? Approach Future speculation using wearable technology Create a speculative body technology that interacts with our sensory input or output. This device could enhance the way we see, limit our ability to smell or hear&amp;hellip;This device could be useful for a future version of our world, or another world/society from our imagination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speculative Thinking</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2017_speculative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2017_speculative/</guid>
      <description>Speculative Thinking Design Research | 2016, Personal Work  My Design Policy Speculative Fusion of Design and Science The following chart is my own thought of the speculative fusion of design and science. In the business field, we have been creating probable futures using industrial solutions. Currently, through a collaboration with designers, technologists and business strategists, we can imagine and develop further plausible futures based on emerging technologies.
Additionally, we must speculate possible futures that research-level technologies promise, and discuss the cultural and political mechanisms behind them to overcome our 21st-century problems.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>