<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MTA Smart Metrocard</title>
      <link>/project/2018_mta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_mta/</guid>
      <description>background The NYC metro system has remained unchanged for decades. Users of NYC subway sometimes have uncomfortable experiences; the lost time of waiting in line to buy a metrocard, touching a dirty machine, dirty platform and so on.
The following chart (source) shows that Ridership through ride-sharing services like Uber and Lyft has increased, while subway and bus ridership has declined. App-based services are based on a great UX and are increasing their users dramatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES</title>
      <link>/project/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>Background After the deregulation, which direction should the electric power company aim for? In 2016, full-scale deregulation of the electricity industry in Japan has begun, and a lot of new and emerging companies have entered the electricity market. Chubu Electric Power Company (C-EPCO), one of Japanese electricity utility providers, must shift to a new paradigm of customer service in order to improve its retention capability.
Problem How might we create tight family bonds in recent Japanese families?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>/project/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview After a class call with Sam Eldersveld, Director of Operations Research at Uber, we learned that, Uber thinks the perfect pickup is the most important factor of the User Experience. The moment of pickup is when the driver and the rider meet for the first time. Both drivers and riders are nervous and frustrating in this moment because drivers want to finish the work without trouble and riders want to get to the destination quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collective Juice</title>
      <link>/project/2018_collective/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_collective/</guid>
      <description>Overview Demo Video   Project Information  Phase / Period  Concept, Design, Build, Evaluate 10 / 2018 (4 weeks)  Team  Researcher(Me), Professor Harpreet Sareen  Method / Technology  Ideation from 1D to 5D Arduino, processing  Output  Physical prototype   Objective How might we collect responses to questions that can only be answered by humans? As the development of technology, we can find many answers online within just a second.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUMAN EXPERIENCE FOR TRANSHUMAN</title>
      <link>/project/2018_speculative/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_speculative/</guid>
      <description>Concept XHuman: Educational Headset for transhumans to Experience “Human” in 2075         
Project Information  Phase / Period  Concept, Design, Build Period* 10&amp;frasl;2018 (2 weeks)  Team / Role  Researcher(Me), Professor  Method  Future Cone, Future&amp;rsquo;s Wheel, Timeline, Persona, Empathy Map, Storyboard, technological research
  Output* Physical prototype, User&amp;rsquo;s Manual  Objective How can Humans and Transhumans coexist towards a sustainable society in 2075?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORGANIC MUSIC VISUALIZER</title>
      <link>/project/2018_organic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_organic/</guid>
      <description>Overview Demo Video   Project Information  Phase / Period  Concept, Design, Build 10 / 2018 (1 Day)  Team / Role  Sole Project Maker, Coder  Method / Technology  Iterative coding html5, css3, javascript, three.js [Link] Demo is here
--</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM WATSON COGNITIVE ENTERPRISE APP</title>
      <link>/project/2016_watson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2016_watson/</guid>
      <description>Overview IBM Watson cognitive application We delivered an initial phase of a cognitive Watson Advisor solution using agile engineering approach. MHI engineers can inspect and take action for risks of their projects in advance without long industry experience. They reduced the time taken by the worker&amp;rsquo;s task by 30% as a result.
Final UI gallery (click to zoom)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Supermarket 2020</title>
      <link>/project/2016_inageya/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2016_inageya/</guid>
      <description>Overview Demo Video   As a facilitator of design thinking, our team designed a 2-days intensive design workshop and created a concept of supermarket of the next-generation. Our concept is that customers and their families can turn their household worries into fun and create their sustainable local communities together.
In the last activity, we defined next To-Dos and achieved a consensus beyond all departments of Inageya. Finally, the client could go forward to a next step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LimpiDual Touch</title>
      <link>/project/2009_llimpidual/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2009_llimpidual/</guid>
      <description>Overview Demo Video   Project Information  Phase / Period  Concept, Design, Build, Evaluate 04/2007 - 03/2009 (2 years)  Team / My Role  Researcher: Masaki Iwabuchi Professor: Takeshi Naemura (Professor of the University of Tokyo)  Method / Technology  Technology Research, Iterative Prototyping Touch Interface, Non-Organic Transparent EL Display, OpenGL  Output  Research Paper, User Evaluation Sheet   Inspiration What if we can display information on a transparent surface?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>