<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ChanoMa</title>
      <link>/project/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>Overview   ChanoMa (means &amp;ldquo;Living Room&amp;rdquo;) is a service for a dual-income households with a children whose age is under 9 years old to tighten family bonds.
Special features of this service is the following:
 Play with children when parents are busy  because working mother’s life is terrible  Record and share children’s daily responses  because parents don’t understand children well   This is a client work for C-EP (Chubu Electric Power), which supplies electricity to 10 million households in Japan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parsons Event App Redesign</title>
      <link>/project/2019_parsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2019_parsons/</guid>
      <description> Project Overview   Final UI     
Visual Design System   Design Process                           
Learning   Project Information  Phase / Period  Concept, Design, Build 10 / 2018 (7 Day)  Team / Role  Sole Project Researcher, Designer  Method / Technology  Design Thinking   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Breathing Chair</title>
      <link>/project/2018_breathing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_breathing/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview I&amp;rsquo;m submitting this project to ACM SIGGRAPH 2019 Posters.
  We present a Breathing Chair that changes its state and shape to prevent current sedentary lifestyle and help in shaping a healthy living habit. The Breathing chair tracks how long people have been sitting, and its surface swells physically like a mammal’s lung when people sit in the Breathing Chair for a long time. In so doing, it nudges people to stand up gently to avoid health risks of prolonged sitting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Information Aesthetics</title>
      <link>/project/2019_viz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2019_viz/</guid>
      <description>Overview I&amp;rsquo;m taking the class of &amp;ldquo;Data Visualization and Information Aesthetics&amp;rdquo; at Parsons School of Design. In this class, I will create a total of four posters and two interactive visualization projects.
In the first half of the semester, I created three posters for specific topics such as Man-made product, Nature and Society. I learned the basic techniques of data visualization in a series of design processes from ideation, source data discovery to iterative prototyping.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>/project/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview I had the opportunity to join the Research Methods in Interaction Design course at the School of Visual Arts. Our instructor Jodi Leo, Executive Director of User Experience at Critical Mass, led us to collaborate with the Research team at Uber to optimize efficiency for Uber drivers during the pick up at the JFK airport.
My Role I conducted interviews with Uber drivers, conducted secondary research, developed personas, project management, synthesis, concept/use case design, and designed the presentation narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AR Businesscard</title>
      <link>/project/2018_ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Sep 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_ar/</guid>
      <description> Demo Video   Project Information  Phase / Period  Concept, Design, Build 102/ 2018 (1 week)  Team / Role  Sole Project Maker, Coder  Method / Technology  Iterative coding Unity, Vuforia, C++              -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HUMAN EXPERIENCE FOR TRANSHUMAN</title>
      <link>/project/2018_speculative/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_speculative/</guid>
      <description>XHuman: Educational Headset for transhumans to Experience “Human” in 2075 XHuman is an educational headset for transhumans who inplants superintelligence into their left brain which works for language, memory, calculation. This gadget stimulates your brain electrically and temporarily stops the neurotransmission between the brain chip and the brain. This feature enables transhumans to think as “Humans.&amp;rdquo;
        
How can Humans and Transhumans coexist towards a sustainable society in 2075?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORGANIC MUSIC VISUALIZER</title>
      <link>/project/2018_organic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_organic/</guid>
      <description> Project Overview    Coded a sound visualizer which enables music experience more organic.
            
Project Information  Phase / Period  Concept, Design, Build 10 / 2018 (1 Day)  Team / Role  Sole Project Maker, Coder  Method / Technology  Iterative coding html5, css3, javascript, three.js   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LimpiDual Touch</title>
      <link>/project/2009_llimpidual/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Mar 2009 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2009_llimpidual/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview    LimpiDual Touch is the emerging interactive transparent display. Users can operate from the rear side of the screen while seeing both displayed images and their fingers. This feature resolves a finger occlusion problem. Additionally, it also works for multiple users. Two users can share an identical display from both sides and control displayed objects at one time. This feature will apply to a collaborative work and an entertainment application.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>