<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolios on iwabm on github</title>
    <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Portfolios on iwabm on github</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy;2017 Masaki Iwabuchi</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Speculative Thinking</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/concept/2017_speculative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/concept/2017_speculative/</guid>
      <description> 2017, Design Process Study
Private Work
Defined and still exploring the experience design process of the 21st Century. Credit Project contribution: Concept
Period: 08/2017
Role: Researcher
Team: Researcher (Me)
Main Output: Methodology Map </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM STUDIO BOARD</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/graphics/2016_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/graphics/2016_studio/</guid>
      <description> 2016, Graphic Design | Professional Work Respect traditional IBM design philosophy Reflect new IBM design environment and culture Design and Prototyping Apply to the atmosphere of studio Credit Project contribution: Concept, Develop, Deliver
Period: 12/2015 - 01/2016
Role: Graphic Designer
Method: Design Thinking
Team: Sole Project
Release: 01/2016 - until now
Main Output: Profile Board </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>INAGEYA</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/concept/2016_inageya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/concept/2016_inageya/</guid>
      <description>2016, Strategic Concept | Professional Work Design Question:
What is &amp;ldquo;beyond&amp;rdquo; supermarket? Under a situation that society and family structures are changing and a role of supermarket also needs to change in Japan, clients were struggling for planning a strong concept of a next-generation supermarket in 2020 with consideration for a sustainable ecosystem and of course customer-first.
Design Thinking: Dive into &amp;ldquo;the user&amp;rdquo; Using IBM Design Thinking, we supported to ideate a brand-new future user experience and defined the concept of next-gen supermarket only in 2 days intensive design camp.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/service--ux/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/service--ux/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>2015, Experience Concept | Academic Work
Design Question: How can we improve experience of driver? Joined 5 weeks MFA Interaction Design Program of User Research Methods in SVA, US. Woriking in teams, we’ve joined a real project with Uber and proposed UX to solve current issues. I’ve learned the fundamentals of user research techniques and the sense of UX in collaboration with global students. The program was following.
Experience Design from Observing Learned methodologies and techniques of the research in a lecture (Week 1).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PARSONS SUMMER</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/graphics/2015_parsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/graphics/2015_parsons/</guid>
      <description>2015, Graphic Design | Academic Work Learn Graphic Design Technique To learn basic skills and philosophy of graphic design, I Took 3-weeks Advanced Graphic Design Summer Program in Parsons the new school of Design, US. During intensive 3-weeks project-based course, I delivered 6 projects; Poster Design, Bookjacket Design, Book Design, Timeline Design, App Design and Identity Design.
Poster Design Using only type, made a poster which explains how to do something specific.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daifuku</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/service--ux/2015_daifuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/service--ux/2015_daifuku/</guid>
      <description>2015, Corporate Website | Professional Work Service Concept Customers can know DAIFUKU’s strength intuitively and get same services from anywhere in the world.
Challenge Clients thought their website was becoming obsolete and wanted to enhance their brand using current web technologies and user-centered disciplines. And Daifuku has 20 branches in the world, so they wanted to provide global integrated contents and operations.
Approach Based on a service design approach, we designed and proposed from a business organization to UX / UI and an infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM CSC</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/concept/2014_csc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/concept/2014_csc/</guid>
      <description>2014, Pro Bono Consulting | Professional Work Challenge IBM CSC(Corporate Service Corp) is one-month pro bono consulting program for developing countries addressing Energy, Economic Development, Transportation, Education, and Healthcare. I’ve applied for this program and tackled the problem of Gender Violence(GV) in Mexico. The 5 IBMers from UK, Germany, India, Taiwan and Japan(me) have worked for IAPEM(Institution of Public Admin. of Mexico State). IAPEM manages the rape crisis centers in Mexico State and provides administration and prompt of justice related to GV.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sundai</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/service--ux/2012_sundai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2012 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/service--ux/2012_sundai/</guid>
      <description>2012, Corporate Website | Professional Work Design Question:
How to make latest service ecosystem? Clients’ website was obsoleted and clients wanted to grow their core customers using current web technologies and usability disciplines. Of course they’d like to reach these objectives in an efficient operation.
User Centered Design The project has reformed an overall user experience of “SUNDAI” website and delivered the new visual design for PCs and smartphones. This includes web strategy consulting, front-end design and development, workflow design, existing data transition, CMS(Contents Management System) development and maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CompAge</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/service--ux/2011_compage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/service--ux/2011_compage/</guid>
      <description>2011, Web Service | Professional Work Design Question: How can we accelerate Startups? Many Japanese startups need impressive graphics for their businesses but almost all companies don’t have in-house designers. I wanted to support these companies and provide the field in which designers can show their talents.
Design for Clients, Designers and Users Using CompAge, clients can hold graphic design competitions easily and cheaply. CompAge is consisted of following 3 key users.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LimpiDual Touch</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/digital-media/2009_limpidual/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Mar 2009 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/portfolio/digital-media/2009_limpidual/</guid>
      <description>2009, Interactive Media | Academic Work
Product Concept Users can interact from the rear side of the display without a finger occlusion problem.  
challenge Direct-touch input enables intuitive operation, and touch panels have been mounted on various devices. However, finger occlusion becomes one of the problems when a user touches the display from the front side.
Approach I’ve proposed the emerging interactive transparent display named ‘‘LimpiDual Touch’’. Users can operate from the rear side of the screen while seeing both displayed images and their fingers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>