<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>uxui on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>/tags/uxui/</link>
    <description>Recent content in uxui on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/uxui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MTA Smart Metrocard</title>
      <link>/project/2018_mta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_mta/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview Current research (source) shows that subway and bus ridership has declined while ridership through ride-sharing services like Lyft and Uber has increased. App-based services are based on a great UX and are increasing their users dramatically.
Therefore, to increase a retention rate, MTA needs to provide the user-centered service for the purpose of getting access easily to the metro, on time, without having a bad experience.
 Data: Transportation Trends in NYC   From interviewing with real users, it turned out that NYC commuters sometimes have a frustration that they want to catch a train but cannot because they don&amp;rsquo;t have enough money in the metro card.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES</title>
      <link>/project/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview In 2016, new policy of deregulation of the electricity industry in Japan has begun, and a lot of new and emerging companies and startups have entered the electricity market and acquire users by user-centric services. C-EP must shift to a client first company and provide user-centered services in order to improve its retention capability.  
C-EP is supporting lives of families and we decided a dual-income working mother as a primary user.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>/project/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview We called with Sam Eldersveld, Director of Operations Research at Uber, and we learned that Uber thought the perfect pickup is the most important factor of the User Experience. The moment of pickup is when the driver and the rider meet for the first time. Both drivers and riders are nervous and frustrating in this moment because drivers want to finish the work without trouble and riders want to get to the destination quickly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM WATSON COGNITIVE ENTERPRISE APP</title>
      <link>/project/2016_watson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2016_watson/</guid>
      <description>Overview IBM Watson cognitive application We delivered an initial phase of a cognitive Watson Advisor solution using agile engineering approach. MHI engineers can inspect and take action for risks of their projects in advance without long industry experience. They reduced the time taken by the worker&amp;rsquo;s task by 30% as a result.
Final UI gallery (click to zoom)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>