<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>uxui on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>/tags/uxui/</link>
    <description>Recent content in uxui on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/uxui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MTA Smart METROCARD</title>
      <link>/project/2018_mta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2018_mta/</guid>
      <description>background The NYC metro system has remained unchanged for decades. Users of NYC subway sometimes have uncomfortable experiences; the lost time of waiting in line to buy a metrocard, touching a dirty machine, dirty platform and so on.
The following chart (source) shows that Ridership through ride-sharing services like Uber and Lyft has increased, while subway and bus ridership has declined. App-based services are based on a great UX and are increasing their users dramatically.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES</title>
      <link>/project/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>Objective After the deregulation, which direction should the electric power company aim for? In 2016, full-scale deregulation of the electricity industry in Japan has begun, and a lot of new and emerging companies have entered the electricity market. Chubu Electric Power Company (C-EPCO), a Japanese electricity utility provider for the mid-Chubu region of Honshu island, Japan, must shift to a new paradigm of customer service in order to improve its retention capability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>/project/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>Background Uber wanted to make cities more accessible This was an academic project of Summer Intensive course of User Research Methods in SVA, US. We worked with a director of Uber and interviewed with him in the beginning. We understood one of the main focus of Uber was how drivers and riders find each other and ensure their identity.
    Problem How might we ensure drivers and riders to find each other and confirm their identity perfectly?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM WATSON COGNITIVE ENTERPRISE APP</title>
      <link>/project/2016_watson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2016_watson/</guid>
      <description>Overview IBM Watson cognitive application We delivered an initial phase of a cognitive Watson Advisor solution using agile engineering approach. MHI engineers can inspect and take action for risks of their projects in advance without long industry experience. They reduced the time taken by the worker&amp;rsquo;s task by 30% as a result.
Final UI gallery (click to zoom)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>