<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Uxui on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>http://iwabm.github.io/tags/uxui/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Uxui on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://iwabm.github.io/tags/uxui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MTA Metrocard Redesign</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_mta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_mta/</guid>
      <description>-- MTA Metrocard Redesign UX/UI Design | 2018, Private Work
  *This project is still ongoing Objective How might we make NYC’s subway riding experience more comfortable? The NYC metrocard system has remained unchanged for decades and users of NYC subway sometimes have uncomfortable experiences especially the entrance of subway; the lost time of waiting in line to buy a metrocard, touching a dirty machine and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>-- C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES Service and UX/UI Design | 2017, Professiona Work
  Objective After the deregulation, which direction should the electric power company aim for? In 2016, full-scale deregulation of the electricity industry in Japan has begun, and a lot of new and emerging companies have entered the electricity market. Chubu Electric Power Company (C-EPCO), a Japanese electricity utility provider for the mid-Chubu region of Honshu island, Japan, must shift to a new paradigm of customer service in order to improve its retention capability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Watson cognitive enterprise app</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2016_mhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2016_mhi/</guid>
      <description>-- IBM Watson cognitive enterprise app Enterprise Application Design | 2016, Professional Work  Objective How can MHI engineers make the RFP inspection process more effectively? RFP inspection is important work for Mitsubishi Heavy Industries, Ltd. (MHI) engineers to estimate risks in advance and deliver the project in a healthy way. However, it needs much knowledge and takes long time to do it accurately under the pressure of a deadline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>-- UBER UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN UX/UI Design | 2015, Academic Work  Objective How can we improve the experience of Uber drivers? Joined 5 weeks MFA Interaction Design Program of User Research Methods in SVA, US. Woriking in teams, we’ve joined a real project with Uber and proposed UX to solve current issues. I’ve learned the fundamentals of user research techniques and the sense of UX in collaboration with global students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daifuku Experience</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2015_daifuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2015_daifuku/</guid>
      <description>-- DAIFUKU EXPERIENCE UX/UI Design | 2015, Professiona Work  Objective How does DAIFUKU build a globally unified brand? Clients thought their website was becoming obsolete and wanted to enhance their brand using current web technologies and user-centered disciplines. And Daifuku has 20 branches in the world, so they wanted to provide global integrated contents and operations.
Concept Redesign DAIFUKU corporate website and operations From the perspective of Business, Design and Technology, we designed and proposed from a business organization to UX / UI and an infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>