<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>uxui on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>/tags/uxui/</link>
    <description>Recent content in uxui on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/uxui/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ChanoMa</title>
      <link>/project/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>Overview service for a dual-income households with a small children to tighten family bonds. We decided a dual-income working mother as a primary user because 49% of households are dual-income families in urban area in Japan. --      -- After the implementation. we performed a qualitative and quantitative user evaluation and 75% of participants evaluated &amp;ldquo;Very Positive&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Positive&amp;rdquo; against the whole concept. Therefore, the client decide to launch this App in the next year cycle with considering qualitative feedback comments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Parsons Event App Redesign</title>
      <link>/project/2019_parsons/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2019_parsons/</guid>
      <description> Project Overview   Final UI     
Visual Design System   Design Process                           
Learning   Project Information  Phase / Period  Concept, Design, Build 10 / 2018 (7 Day)  Team / Role  Sole Project Researcher, Designer  Method / Technology  Design Thinking   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MTA Smart Metrocard</title>
      <link>/tmp/2018_mta/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tmp/2018_mta/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview I personally tried to redesign MTA services because NYC subway riding experience is uncomfortable for me; dirty platform, unexpected stop, morning/evening rush and so on. I conducted the entire design process to specify inconvenient element of the subway and improve services of MTA.
My Role I conducted the whole design process from interviewing with users, defining problem, ideation, prototyping and evaluation.
Background Current research (source) shows that subway and bus ridership has declined while ridership through ride-sharing services like Lyft and Uber has increased.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UBER UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>/project/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Oct 2018 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>Project Overview I had the opportunity to join the Research Methods in Interaction Design course at the School of Visual Arts. Our instructor Jodi Leo, Executive Director of User Experience at Critical Mass, led us to collaborate with the Research team at Uber to optimize efficiency for Uber drivers during the pick up at the JFK airport.
My Role I conducted interviews with Uber drivers, conducted secondary research, developed personas, project management, synthesis, concept/use case design, and designed the presentation narrative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM WATSON COGNITIVE ENTERPRISE APP</title>
      <link>/tmp/2016_watson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tmp/2016_watson/</guid>
      <description>Overview IBM Watson cognitive application We delivered an initial phase of a cognitive Watson Advisor solution using agile engineering approach. MHI engineers can inspect and take action for risks of their projects in advance without long industry experience. They reduced the time taken by the worker&amp;rsquo;s task by 30% as a result.
Final UI gallery (click to zoom)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>