<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://iwabm.github.io/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>-- C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES Service and UX/UI Design | 2017, Professiona Work
  Objective After the deregulation, which direction should the electric power company aim for? In 2016, full-scale deregulation of the electricity industry in Japan has begun, and a lot of new and emerging companies have entered the electricity market. Chubu Electric Power Company (C-EPCO), a Japanese electricity utility provider for the mid-Chubu region of Honshu island, Japan, must shift to a new paradigm of customer service in order to improve its retention capability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MTA Metrocard Redesign</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_mta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_mta/</guid>
      <description>-- MTA Metrocard Redesign UX/UI Design | 2018, Private Work
  *This project is still ongoing Objective How might we make NYC’s subway riding experience more comfortable? The NYC metrocard system has remained unchanged for decades and users of NYC subway sometimes have uncomfortable experiences especially the entrance of subway; the lost time of waiting in line to buy a metrocard, touching a dirty machine and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>-- UBER UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN UX/UI Design | 2015, Academic Work  Objective How can we improve the experience of Uber drivers? Joined 5 weeks MFA Interaction Design Program of User Research Methods in SVA, US. Woriking in teams, we’ve joined a real project with Uber and proposed UX to solve current issues. I’ve learned the fundamentals of user research techniques and the sense of UX in collaboration with global students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Watson cognitive enterprise app</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2016_mhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2016_mhi/</guid>
      <description>-- IBM Watson cognitive enterprise app Enterprise Application Design | 2016, Professional Work  Overview IBM Watson cognitive application We delivered an initial phase of a cognitive Watson Advisor solution using agile engineering approach. MHI engineers can inspect and take action for risks of their projects in advance without long industry experience. They reduced the time taken by the worker&amp;rsquo;s task by 30% as a result.
                                         Clients needs ‘‘innovative and unique UI’’ to show brand-new experience internally, so we experimented various UIs with real users and applied the unique interaction inspired by the cube.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collective Juice</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_collective/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2011 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_collective/</guid>
      <description>-- COLLECTIVE JUICE Interaction Design | 2018, Academic Work  Overview Collect people&amp;rsquo;s emotions and visualie them as an collective juice Collective Juice is a physical product that collects different user&amp;rsquo;s emotions and tone together to reveal and visualizes the “mood” of the group/community.  
Phase
Concept, Design, Build, Deliver, Evaluate
Period
10/2018 (4 weeks)
Team
Researcher(Me), Professor
Role
Researcher
 Method
Iterative Ideation from 1D to 5D</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organic Sound Visualizer</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_three/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_three/</guid>
      <description> Organic Sound Visualizer 1 Day Programming | 2018, Academic Work  Concept How might we make the experience of listening music more organic?   Phase
Concept, Design, Build
Period
10/2018 (1 Day)
Team
Sole Project
Role
Maker, Coder
 Method
Iterative coding
Technology
html5, css3, javascript, three.js
Output
[Link] Demo is here
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LimpiDual Touch</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2009_limpidual/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2009_limpidual/</guid>
      <description>-- LIMPIDUAL TOUCH Interaction Design | 2009, Academic Work  Overview Designed and proposed interactive limpid display with dual-sided touch sensing. LimpiDual Touch is the emerging interactive transparent display. Users can operate from the rear side of the screen while seeing both displayed images and their fingers. This feature resolves a finger occlusion problem. Additionally, it also works for multiple users. Two users can share an identical display from both sides and control displayed objects at one time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human experience for Transhuman</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_singular/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2008 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2018_singular/</guid>
      <description>-- Human experience for Transhuman Speculative Design | 2018, Academic Work | ONGOING  Concept XHuman: Educational Headset for transhumans to Experience “Human” in 2075 XHuman is an educational headset for transhumans who inplants superintelligence into their left brain. This gadget stimulates your brain electrically and temporarily stops the neurotransmission between the brain chip and the brain. This feature enables transhumans to think as “Humans”.
Since transhuman’s brain chip is implanted in your left brain (work for language, memory, calculation), so be sure to wear it on the left brain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUTURE SUPERMARKET DESIGN INAGEYA</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2016_inageya/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jan 2008 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/2016_inageya/</guid>
      <description>-- FUTURE SUPERMARKET DESIGN INAGEYA Service Design | 2016, Professional Work
  Overview Next-Generation Supermarket in 2020 As a facilitator of design thinking, our team designed a 2-days intensive design workshop and created a concept of supermarket of the next-generation. Our concept is that customers and their families can turn their household worries into fun and create their sustainable local communities together.
In the last activity, we defined next To-Dos and achieved a consensus beyond all departments of Inageya.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>