<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Masaki Iwabuchi</title>
    <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Masaki Iwabuchi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:25:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://iwabm.github.io/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2017_cepco/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2017_cepco/</guid>
      <description>-- C-EP CONSUMER SERVICES Service Design | 2017, Professiona Work
  Objective After the deregulation, which direction should the electric power company aim for? In 2016, full-scale deregulation of the electricity industry in Japan has begun, and a lot of new and emerging companies have entered the electricity market. Chubu Electric Power Company (C-EPCO), a Japanese electricity utility provider for the mid-Chubu region of Honshu island, Japan, must shift to a new paradigm of customer service in order to improve its retention capability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Watson cognitive enterprise app</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2016_mhi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2016_mhi/</guid>
      <description>-- IBM Watson cognitive enterprise app Enterprise Application Design | 2016, Professional Work  Objective How can MHI engineers make the RFP inspection process more effectively? RFP inspection is important work for Mitsubishi Heavy Industries, Ltd. (MHI) engineers to estimate risks in advance and deliver the project in a healthy way. However, it needs much knowledge and takes long time to do it accurately under the pressure of a deadline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Collective Juice</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/digital-media/2018_collective/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/digital-media/2018_collective/</guid>
      <description>-- COLLECTIVE JUICE Interaction Design | 2018, Academic Work  Objective What is the question that can only be answered by humans during the AI era? Everyday we are googling many questions and we can get answer immediately. Also, recently AI can answer more and more sophisticated questions. However, I think still there are things that can only be answered by people such as fuzzy, real-time and people-oriented questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MTA Metrocard Redesign</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2018_mta/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2018_mta/</guid>
      <description>-- MTA Metrocard Redesign UX/UI Design | 2018, Private Work
  *This project is still ongoing Objective How might we make NYC’s subway riding experience more comfortable? The NYC metrocard system has remained unchanged for decades and users of NYC subway sometimes have uncomfortable experiences especially the entrance of subway; the lost time of waiting in line to buy a metrocard, touching a dirty machine and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uber UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2015_uber/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2015_uber/</guid>
      <description>-- UBER UX RESEARCH AND DESIGN UX/UI Design | 2015, Academic Work  Objective How can we improve the experience of Uber drivers? Joined 5 weeks MFA Interaction Design Program of User Research Methods in SVA, US. Woriking in teams, we’ve joined a real project with Uber and proposed UX to solve current issues. I’ve learned the fundamentals of user research techniques and the sense of UX in collaboration with global students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Human experience for Transhuman</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2018_singular/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2018_singular/</guid>
      <description>-- Human experience for Transhuman Speculative Design | 2018, Academic Work | ONGOING  Concept Human experience for Transhuman in 2075 Not to forget &amp;ldquo;human&amp;rdquo; emotion, transhuman children wear the device in their head. This suspends their implanted AI and They can think “as human”.
Transhuman children go to transhuman-only school and this experience is taught in the &amp;ldquo;human history&amp;rdquo; class.
User&amp;rsquo;s Manual Settings What kind of tools are used by children who were born transhuman in the age of post-singularity?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FUTURE SUPERMARKET DESIGN INAGEYA</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2016_inageya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2016_inageya/</guid>
      <description>-- FUTURE SUPERMARKET DESIGN INAGEYA Business Design | 2016, Professional Work
  Objective What should Inageya do to go &amp;ldquo;beyond&amp;rdquo; supermarket? Inagea is a long-established supermarket in Japan. However, in a situation that society and family structures are changing, a role of supermarket also needs to change in Japan. Clients were struggling for planning a strong concept of a next-generation supermarket in 2020 with consideration for a sustainable ecosystem from producers to consumers and of course customer-first.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LimpiDual Touch</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/digital-media/2009_limpidual/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/digital-media/2009_limpidual/</guid>
      <description>-- LIMPIDUAL TOUCH Interaction Design | 2009, Academic Work  Overview Designed and proposed interactive limpid display with dual-sided touch sensing.   I’ve proposed the emerging interactive transparent display named ‘‘LimpiDual Touch’’. Users can operate from the rear side of the screen while seeing both displayed images and their fingers. This feature resolves a finger occlusion problem. Additionally, LimpiDual Touch also works for multiple users. Two users can share an identical display from both sides and control displayed objects at one time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Daifuku Experience</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2015_daifuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2015 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/service--ux/2015_daifuku/</guid>
      <description>-- DAIFUKU EXPERIENCE UX/UI Design | 2015, Professiona Work  Objective How does DAIFUKU build a globally unified brand? Clients thought their website was becoming obsolete and wanted to enhance their brand using current web technologies and user-centered disciplines. And Daifuku has 20 branches in the world, so they wanted to provide global integrated contents and operations.
Concept Redesign DAIFUKU corporate website and operations From the perspective of Business, Design and Technology, we designed and proposed from a business organization to UX / UI and an infrastructure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organic Sound Visualizer</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/code/2018_three/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/code/2018_three/</guid>
      <description> Organic Sound Visualizer Programming as Performance | 2018, Academic Work  Concept What will happen if the boundaries between music and living things blur?   Phase
Concept, Design, Build
Period
10/2018 (1 Week)
Team
Sole Project
Role
Maker, Coder
 Method
Iterative coding
Technology
html5, css3, javascript, three.js
Output
[Link] Demo is here
         </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Ephemerality</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/graphics/2018_processing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Feb 2018 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/graphics/2018_processing/</guid>
      <description>Artificial Ephemerality Programming as Art | 2018, Academic Work  Objective How do we express “ephemerality” artificially?    -- - Press &#34;S&#34; to save the current screenshot to your desktop.
- Press &#34;T&#34; to turn on/off the music.
- Press &#34;P&#34; to pause the generation process.  Phase
Concept, Design, Build
Period
08/2018 (1 Week)
Team
Sole Project
Role
Maker, Coder
What I did
Define Experience Concept</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Speculative Thinking</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2017_speculative/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2017_speculative/</guid>
      <description>Speculative Thinking Design Research | 2016, Personal Work  My Design Policy Speculative Fusion of Design and Science The following chart is my own thought of the speculative fusion of design and science. In the business field, we have been creating probable futures using industrial solutions. Currently, through a collaboration with designers, technologists and business strategists, we can imagine and develop further plausible futures based on emerging technologies.
Additionally, we must speculate possible futures that research-level technologies promise, and discuss the cultural and political mechanisms behind them to overcome our 21st-century problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM JAPAN DESIGNER&#39;S BOARD</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/graphics/2016_studio/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/graphics/2016_studio/</guid>
      <description>  -- IBM JAPAN DESIGNER&#39;S BOARD Graphic Design | 2016, Professional Work  Objective How might IBM designers express our new design culture?   Phase
Concept, Develop, Deliver
Period
12/2015 - 01/2016
Team
Sole Project
Role
Graphic Designer
What I did
Define Experience Concept
-- Method
IBM Design Thinking
Output
Profile Board
Product Golive
01/2016 - until now
  Concept Designed the profile board to show talents in the Tokyo Studio  Result Apply to the atmosphere of our Tokyo studio    Design Process Starting point was a respect to the traditional IBM philosophy  Additionally, we reflect new IBM design culture  1st &amp;amp; 2nd prototype              3nd prototype                Physical prototype and finalizing                </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Corporate Service Corps</title>
      <link>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2014_csc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2014 18:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://iwabm.github.io/work/concept/2014_csc/</guid>
      <description>-- IBM Corporate Service Corps Civic Service Design | 2014, Professional Work  Overview Tackled with a gender violence problem in Mexico and proposed strategies to Protect Victims and Prevent Crimes. IBM CSC(Corporate Service Corp) is one-month pro bono consulting program for developing countries addressing Energy, Economic Development, Transportation, Education, and Healthcare. I participated in the IBM pro bono Corporate Service Corps, addressing social issues in developing countries. I was one of a cross-border global IBM team in Mexico that sought to tackle the problems of gender violence by collaborating with IAPEM (the Mexico State Public Administration).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>